The Source image we'll be using today is
今日使用するソース画像は
a 'table setting' jpeg. It is 602 kilobytes
「テーブルセッティング」jpeg。 602キロバイトです
and it's currently 1678 by 1119 pixels
現在は 1678 x 1119 ピクセルです
wide, much too big to be using in our web
幅が広く、ウェブで使用するには大きすぎます
page.
ページ。
I have this online Pixlr E photo editor
私はこのオンライン Pixlr E フォト エディターを持っています
up. It is a free tool. You're limited to a
上。 無料のツールです。 あなたはに制限されています
certain number of saves per day so you
1 日あたりの保存回数が決まっているので、
may have to spread out your work over
あなたの仕事を広げなければならないかもしれません
several days. Let's go ahead and start by
数日。 先に進みましょう
opening...
オープニング...
our source image.
私たちのソース画像。
Now for this particular activity, we're
この特定のアクティビティについては、
going to be using a 2:1 ratio so
2:1 の比率を使用するので、
grab the cropping tool,
トリミングツールをつかみ、
check the size. Our large image
サイズを確認してください。 私たちの大きな画像
is going to be 1500 wide
幅は1500になります
and half of that is 750 tall. Now we're
その半分の高さは 750 です。 今、私たちは
going to use art direction to select the
アートディレクションを使用して選択します
part of this image we want to use for
この画像の使用したい部分
the large screen.
大画面。
I'm going to slide it up a little bit
少し上にスライドさせてみます
so those glasses are centered.
これらのメガネは中央にあります。
Then I'm going to hit enter on the
次にEnterキーを押します
keyboard. That crops it off. Notice the
キーボード。 それはそれを切り取ります。 注意してください
width and the height over here.
ここの幅と高さ。
I'm now ready to save that image.
これで、その画像を保存する準備が整いました。
We will be using a web P, low quality
低品質のWeb Pを使用します
at around 50%. That's going to give you
約 50% で。 それはあなたを与えるつもりです
a really small image.
本当に小さい画像。
Let's save it as 'hero -'' and this will
「hero -」として保存してみましょう。
be 'large'.
「大」であること。
We'll save it out to the desktop.
デスクトップに保存します。
We can now return to our original image
これで元の画像に戻ることができます
by clicking up here on open.
ここをクリックして開きます。
Let's select the cropping tool again,
切り抜きツールをもう一度選択してみましょう。
choose a size this time for medium screens.
今回は中画面用のサイズを選択します。
We'll be using 1000 wide by 500 tall for
幅 1000 x 高さ 500 を使用します
this activity.
この活動。
I'll change my cropping for the medium
メディアのトリミングを変更します
screens. I'm going to focus more
画面。 もっと集中していきます
on the glasses and the napkin, so I'll
メガネとナプキンに
put the glasses over here at the right.
眼鏡をここの右側に置いてください。
This is 'Art Direction' to  focus
注目するのは「アートディレクション」
the user on what I want them to see.
私が彼らに見せたいものについてのユーザー。
Click enter on the keyboard.
キーボードの Enter をクリックします。
Notice that the width and the height are
幅と高さが
correct.
正しい。
Let's save it.
保存しましょう。
Once again we'll do web P, quality low
もう一度、Web P を行います。品質は低くなります。
and hero
そしてヒーロー
- medium.
- 中くらい。
Save it and we've got two done.
それを保存すると、2 つの作業が完了します。
Let's now return to the open state,
開いた状態に戻りましょう。
grab the cropping tool,
トリミングツールをつかみ、
size... and now for phones, or very small
サイズ...そして今では電話用、または非常に小さい
screens, we'll be doing 500 wide by 250
画面では、500 幅 x 250 を実行します。
tall.
高い。
This time I'm going to really focus
今回はかなり集中していきます
in
の
on this smallest glass and maybe this
この最小のガラスと多分これ
Angel here in the napkin.
ナプキンの天使。
That'll be my Art Direction crop for
それは私のアートディレクションの切り抜きになります
this one, Press enter.
これ、エンターを押してください。
Save.
保存。
We choosew low quality, save as hero
低品質を選択し、ヒーローとして保存します
- small
- 小さい
You now have in your desktop a series of
これで、デスクトップに一連の
three images
3 つの画像
each at a different width and height but
それぞれ幅と高さが異なりますが、
all using a two by one ratio. Each of
すべて 2 対 1 の比率を使用します。 それぞれの
them saved at fifty percent quality. Look
それらは 50% の品質で保存されました。 見て
at the size of these 37, 20, 8. If you
これらの 37、20、8 のサイズで。
remember, our original image
覚えておいて、私たちの元のイメージ
was just over 600 so we've done some
ちょうど 600 を超えていたので、
amazing data savings by reducing the
削減による驚くべきデータ節約
size, choosing a webp format, and setting
サイズ、webp 形式の選択、および設定
the quality at low.
低品質。